Frank Stick Papers and Artwork PC.5089
Frank Stick Papers and Artwork
- Artwork, circa 1910s-1966; 45506; Stick, Frank
  - Fish Watercolors, UNK; 7956; 33GRF-1; 5000.4.570; PC.5089; Painting; Stick, Frank
    - Albacore Tuna, Thunnus alalunga, PC.5089.1.269; Stick, Frank (Item Albacore Tuna, Thunnus alalunga)
    - Spotted Sea Trout, Cynoscion nebulosus, PC.5089.1.270; Stick, Frank (Item Spotted Sea Trout, Cynoscion nebulosus)
    - Red Snapper, Lutjanus campechanus, PC.5089.1.271; Stick, Frank (Item Red Snapper, Lutjanus campechanus)
    - Swordfish, Xiphias gladius, PC.5089.1.272; Stick, Frank (Item Swordfish, Xiphias gladius)
    - Wahoo, Acanthocybium solanderi, PC.5089.1.273; Stick, Frank (Item Wahoo, Acanthocybium solanderi)
    - Swordfish, Xiphias gladius, PC.5089.1.274; Stick, Frank (Item Swordfish, Xiphias gladius)
    - Silver Perch, Bairdiella chrysoura, PC.5089.1.275; Stick, Frank (Item Silver Perch, Bairdiella chrysoura)
    - Striped Mojarra, Diapterus plumieri, PC.5089.1.276; Stick, Frank (Item Striped Mojarra, Diapterus plumieri)
    - Yellowfin Grouper, Mycteroperca venenosa, PC.5089.1.277; Stick, Frank (Item Yellowfin Grouper, Mycteroperca venenosa)
    - Coney, Epinephelus Fulvus, PC.5089.1.278; Stick, Frank (Item Coney, Epinephelus Fulvus)
    - Atlantic Mackerel, Scomber scombrus, PC.5089.1.279; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Mackerel, Scomber scombrus)
    - Bluefin Tuna, Thunnus thynnus, PC.5089.1.280; Stick, Frank (Item Bluefin Tuna, Thunnus thynnus)
    - Atlantic Menhaden, Brevoortia tyrannus, PC.5089.1.281; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Menhaden, Brevoortia tyrannus)
    - Ballyhoo, Hemiramphus brasiliensis, PC.5089.1.282; Stick, Frank (Item Ballyhoo, Hemiramphus brasiliensis)
    - Balao, Halfbeak, Hyporhamphus unifasciatus, PC.5089.1.283; Stick, Frank (Item Balao, Halfbeak, Hyporhamphus unifasciatus)
    - Houndfish, Atlantic Needlefish, Strongylura marina, PC.5089.1.284; Stick, Frank (Item Houndfish, Atlantic Needlefish, Strongylura marina)
    - Longhorn Sculpin, Myoxcephalus octodecemspinosus, PC.5089.1.285; Stick, Frank (Item Longhorn Sculpin, Myoxcephalus octodecemspinosus)
    - Greater Barracuda, Sphyraena barracuda, PC.5089.1.286; Stick, Frank (Item Greater Barracuda, Sphyraena barracuda)
    - Blue Marlin, Makaira nigricans, PC.5089.1.287; Stick, Frank (Item Blue Marlin, Makaira nigricans)
    - Ladyfish, Elops saurus, PC.5089.1.288; Stick, Frank (Item Ladyfish, Elops saurus)
    - Shortfin Mako, Isurus oxyrinchus, PC.5089.1.289; Stick, Frank (Item Shortfin Mako, Isurus oxyrinchus)
    - King Mackerel, Scomberomorus cavalla, PC.5089.1.290; Stick, Frank (Item King Mackerel, Scomberomorus cavalla)
    - Great Barracuda, Sphyraena barracuda, PC.5089.1.291; Stick, Frank (Item Great Barracuda, Sphyraena barracuda)
    - Hogfish, Lachnolaimus maximus, PC.5089.1.292; Stick, Frank (Item Hogfish, Lachnolaimus maximus)
    - Dolphin, Coryphaena hippururs, PC.5089.1.293; Stick, Frank (Item Dolphin, Coryphaena hippururs)
    - Tarpon, Megalops atlantica, PC.5089.1.294; Stick, Frank (Item Tarpon, Megalops atlantica)
    - Sailfish, Istiophorus platypterus, PC.5089.1.295; Stick, Frank (Item Sailfish, Istiophorus platypterus)
    - Longbill Spearfish, Tetrapterus pfluegeri, PC.5089.1.296; Stick, Frank (Item Longbill Spearfish, Tetrapterus pfluegeri)
    - Atlantic Bonito, Sarda sarda, PC.5089.1.297; Stick, Frank (Item Atlantic Bonito, Sarda sarda)
    - Agujon, Tylosurus acus, PC.5089.1.298; Stick, Frank (Item Agujon, Tylosurus acus)
    - Tarpon, Megalops atlantica, PC.5089.1.299; Stick, Frank (Item Tarpon, Megalops atlantica)
    - Almaco Jack, Seriola rivoliana, PC.5089.1.300; Stick, Frank (Item Almaco Jack, Seriola rivoliana)
    - Blue Marlin, Makaira nigricans, PC.5089.1.301; Stick, Frank (Item Blue Marlin, Makaira nigricans)
    - Wahoo, Acanthocybium solanderi, PC.5089.1.302; Stick, Frank (Item Wahoo, Acanthocybium solanderi)
    - Dolphin, Coryphaena hippurus, PC.5089.1.303; Stick, Frank (Item Dolphin, Coryphaena hippurus)
    - Ladyfish, Elops saurus, PC.5089.1.304; Stick, Frank (Item Ladyfish, Elops saurus)
    - Reeling One In, PC.5089.1.305; Stick, Frank (Item Reeling One In)
    - Bluefish, Pomatomus saltatrix, PC.5089.1.306; Stick, Frank (Item Bluefish, Pomatomus saltatrix)
    - Striped Bass, Morone saxatilis, PC.5089.1.307; Stick, Frank (Item Striped Bass, Morone saxatilis)
    - Rock Sea Bass, Centropristis philadelphica, PC.5089.1.308; Stick, Frank (Item Rock Sea Bass, Centropristis philadelphica)
  - Other Paintings and Illustrations, circa 1910s-1966; 7955; 33GRF-2; 5000.4.571; PC.5089; Painting; Stick, Frank
    - Market Day: Virgin Gorda, PC.5089.2.001; Stick, Frank (Item Market Day: Virgin Gorda)
    - Indian Journey, PC.5089.2.002; Stick, Frank (Item Indian Journey)
    - Puerto Rico, PC.5089.2.003; Stick, Frank (Item Puerto Rico)
    - Sunday Afternoon Fishing, PC.5089.2.004; Stick, Frank (Item Sunday Afternoon Fishing)
    - Egret Rookery, PC.5089.2.005; Stick, Frank (Item Egret Rookery)
    - Chippewa Indians, PC.5089.2.006; Stick, Frank (Item Chippewa Indians)
    - Lily Pond, Frog and Bird, PC.5089.2.007; Stick, Frank (Item Lily Pond, Frog and Bird)
    - The Dorymen, PC.5089.2.008; Stick, Frank (Item The Dorymen)
    - Sir Francis Drake Channel, PC.5089.2.009; Stick, Frank (Item Sir Francis Drake Channel)
    - Tempest, PC.5089.2.010; Stick, Frank (Item Tempest)
    - Rock and Surf, PC.5089.2.011; Stick, Frank (Item Rock and Surf)
    - Summer Squall, PC.5089.2.012; Stick, Frank (Item Summer Squall)
    - Rocky Cove, PC.5089.2.013; Stick, Frank (Item Rocky Cove)
    - Delaware River Rapids, PC.5089.2.014; Stick, Frank (Item Deleware River Rapids)
    - Rocks Off St. John, PC.5089.2.015; Stick, Frank (Item Rocks Off St. John)
    - Portage, PC.5089.2.016; Stick, Frank (Item Portage)
    - Trout Fishing, PC.5089.2.017; Stick, Frank (Item Trout Fishing)
    - Ghost Ship, PC.5089.2.018; Stick, Frank (Item Ghost Ship)
    - Quietude - Isle of Pines, PC.5089.2.019; Stick, Frank (Item Quietude - Isle of Pines)
    - The Fish Trap, PC.5089.2.020; Stick, Frank (Item The Fish Trap)
    - Reflections, PC.5089.2.021; Stick, Frank (Item Reflections)
    - Cittie of Ralegh: Colonist's Cabin, PC.5089.2.022; Stick, Frank (Item Cittie of Ralegh: Colonist's Cabin)
    - Cittie of Ralegh: Keeper's Lodge, PC.5089.2.023; Stick, Frank (Item Cittie of Ralegh: Keeper's Lodge)
    - Cittie of Ralegh: John White House, PC.5089.2.024; Stick, Frank (Item Cittie of Ralegh: John White House)
    - Cittie of Ralegh: Fort Raleigh Museum, PC.5089.2.025; Stick, Frank (Item Cittie of Ralegh: Fort Raleigh Museum)
    - Cittie of Ralegh: Chapel, PC.5089.2.026; Stick, Frank (Item Cittie of Ralegh: Chapel)
    - Cittie of Ralegh: Log Palisade and Guardhouse, PC.5089.2.027; Stick, Frank (Item Cittie of Ralegh: Log Palisade and Guardhouse)
    - Evening Glow, PC.5089.2.028; Stick, Frank (Item Evening Glow)
    - Coming Home / Jackrabbit Attempting Escape From Attacking Hawk, PC.5089.2.029; Stick, Frank (Item Coming Home / Jackrabbit Attempting Escape From Attacking Hawk)
    - Peters Shells Advertisement, PC.5089.2.030; Stick, Frank (Item Peters Shells Advertisement)
    - L.M. Pangburn (Schenectady, New York) 1934 Calendar, PC.5089.2.031; Stick, Frank (Item L.M. Pangburn (Schenectady, New York) 1934 Calendar)
    - An Arctic Tragedy, PC.5089.2.032; Stick, Frank (Item An Arctic Tragedy)
    - James P. Conner, C.P. (Macomb, Illinois) 1925 Calendar, PC.5089.2.033; Stick, Frank (Item James P. Conner, C.P. (Macomb, Illinois) 1925 Calendar)
    - In the Nick of Time, PC.5089.2.034; Stick, Frank (Item In the Nick of Time)
    - Here's Luck, PC.5089.2.035; Stick, Frank (Item Here's Luck)
    - Aubol & Bryan 1919 Calendar, PC.5089.2.036; Stick, Frank (Item Aubol & Bryan 1919 Calendar)
    - Moose Hunting, PC.5089.2.037; Stick, Frank (Item Moose Hunting)
    - Untitled (Two Men Shooting Ducks in a Canoe), PC.5089.2.038; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Shooting Ducks in a Canoe))
    - Joan de Belleville, PC.5089.2.039; Stick, Frank (Item Joan de Belleville)
    - Untitled (Lion and Lioness), PC.5089.2.040; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Lion and Lioness))
    - Back with the Goods, PC.5089.2.041; Stick, Frank (Item Back with the Goods)
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish, Buck in Background), PC.5089.2.042; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish, Buck in Background))
    - Untitled (Two men by a Campfire and Two Men in a Canoe at Night), PC.5089.2.043; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two men by a Campfire and Two Men in a Canoe at Night))
    - The Big Ones Don't Always Get Away, PC.5089.2.044; Stick, Frank (Item The Big Ones Don't Always Get Away)
    - An Exciting Moment, PC.5089.2.045; Stick, Frank (Item An Exciting Moment)
    - Untitled (Two men by a Campfire and Two Men in a Canoe at Night), PC.5089.2.046; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two men by a Campfire and Two Men in a Canoe at Night))
    - The Covered Wagon, PC.5089.2.047; Stick, Frank (Item The Covered Wagon)
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish), PC.5089.2.048; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish))
    - A Retriever, PC.5089.2.049; Stick, Frank (Item A Retriever)
    - A Surprise Attack, PC.5089.2.050; Stick, Frank (Item A Surprise Attack)
    - A King of the Water, PC.5089.2.051; Stick, Frank (Item A King of the Water)
    - The Big Prize, PC.5089.2.052; Stick, Frank (Item The Big Prize)
    - Untitled (Man, Boy, Dog, and Two Horses Plowing, Group of Soldiers in Background), PC.5089.2.053; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man, Boy, Dog, and Two Horses Plowing, Group of Soldiers in Background))
    - Hooked but not Caught, PC.5089.2.054; Stick, Frank (Item Hooked but not Caught)
    - Get the Wolves First, PC.5089.2.055; Stick, Frank (Item Get the Wolves First)
    - Untitled (Man and Woman on Horseback), PC.5089.2.056; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man and Woman on Horseback))
    - Perfectly Satisfied, PC.5089.2.057; Stick, Frank (Item Perfectly Satisfied)
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish, Buck in Background), PC.5089.2.058; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish, Buck in Background))
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish), PC.5089.2.059; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Catching a Fish))
    - Marooned (1928 Calendar), PC.5089.2.060; Stick, Frank (Item Marooned (1928 Calendar))
    - Get the Wolves First (1938 Calendar), PC.5089.2.061; Stick, Frank (Item Get the Wolves First (1938 Calendar))
    - Winchester Furniture Company (Winchester, Virginia) 1940 Calendar, PC.5089.2.062; Stick, Frank (Item Winchester Furniture Company (Winchester, Virginia) 1940 Calendar)
    - 1940 Advertisement Calendar, PC.5089.2.063; Stick, Frank (Item 1940 Advertisement Calendar)
    - Schneider Funeral Home Calendar, PC.5089.2.064; Stick, Frank (Item Schneider Funeral Home Calendar)
    - A Fight to the Finish, PC.5089.2.065; Stick, Frank (Item A Fight to the Finish)
    - Emrich Hardware Co. 1935 Calendar, PC.5089.2.066; Stick, Frank (Item Emrich Hardware Co. 1935 Calendar)
    - Racing the Storm, PC.5089.2.067; Stick, Frank (Item Racing the Storm)
    - A Fight to the Finish, PC.5089.2.068; Stick, Frank (Item A Fight to the Finish)
    - Untitled (Two Men Wave to Rafts Floating Downriver), PC.5089.2.069; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Wave to Rafts Floating Downriver))
    - Quick Buddy Shove Off!, PC.5089.2.070; Stick, Frank (Item Quick Buddy Shove Off!)
    - The Lumberjack, PC.5089.2.071; Stick, Frank (Item The Lumberjack)
    - Come and Get It (1926 Calendar), PC.5089.2.072; Stick, Frank (Item Come and Get It (1926 Calendar))
    - The Unexpected Guest (1930 Calendar), PC.5089.2.073; Stick, Frank (Item The Unexpected Guest (1930 Calendar))
    - Decoyed, PC.5089.2.074; Stick, Frank (Item Decoyed)
    - The Catch of the Season, PC.5089.2.075; Stick, Frank (Item The Catch of the Season)
    - Close Quarters, PC.5089.2.076; Stick, Frank (Item Close Quarters)
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe on Rapids), PC.5089.2.077; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe on Rapids))
    - The Moose Call, PC.5089.2.078; Stick, Frank (Item The Moose Call)
    - Field and Stream September 1909 Cover, PC.5089.2.079; Stick, Frank (Item Field and Stream September 1909 Cover)
    - Field and Stream September 1913 Cover, PC.5089.2.080; Stick, Frank (Item Field and Stream September 1913 Cover)
    - Untitled (Two Dogs and a Man Hunting in Woods Near a Farm), PC.5089.2.081; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Dogs and a Man Hunting in Woods Near a Farm))
    - Untitled (Man and Boy Hunting with Two Dogs), PC.5089.2.082; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man and Boy Hunting with Two Dogs))
    - A Retriever, PC.5089.2.083; Stick, Frank (Item A Retriever)
    - Untitled (Two Men Hunting with a Dog in a Cornfield), PC.5089.2.084; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Hunting with a Dog in a Cornfield))
    - A Viking Mother, PC.5089.2.085; Stick, Frank (Item A Viking Mother)
    - Decoyed, PC.5089.2.086; Stick, Frank (Item Decoyed)
    - Untitled (Family of Four Beside Campfire and Covered Wagon), PC.5089.2.087; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Family of Four Beside Campfire and Covered Wagon))
    - Untitled (Two Men Camping and Cooking by a River), PC.5089.2.088; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Camping and Cooking by a River))
    - Untitled (Man at Campsite Watching Buck Across River), PC.5089.2.089; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man at Campsite Watching Buck Across River))
    - Untitled (Two Men Shoot from a Duck Blind), PC.5089.2.090; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Shoot from a Duck Blind))
    - A Critical Moment, PC.5089.2.091; Stick, Frank (Item A Critical Moment)
    - Security and Trust, PC.5089.2.092; Stick, Frank (Item Security and Trust)
    - "The Stars Look Down On Nature's Chilly White While Hunger Calls the Children of the Night", PC.5089.2.093; Stick, Frank (Item "The Stars Look Down On Nature's Chilly White While Hunger Calls the Children of the Night")
    - Surprised, PC.5089.2.094; Stick, Frank (Item Surprised)
    - A Battle Royal, PC.5089.2.095; Stick, Frank (Item A Battle Royal)
    - A Record Head, PC.5089.2.096; Stick, Frank (Item A Record Head)
    - People's Ideal Fiction Magazine October 1913 Cover, PC.5089.2.097; Stick, Frank (Item People's Ideal Fiction Magazine October 1913 Cover)
    - Playing Him (June 1921 Calendar), PC.5089.2.098; Stick, Frank (Item Playing Him (June 1921 Calendar))
    - Rough and Tumble (February 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.099; Stick, Frank (Item Rough and Tumble (February 1923 Calendar))
    - A Bird in the Hand (April 1916 Calendar), PC.5089.2.100; Stick, Frank (Item A Bird in the Hand (April 1916 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Calling a Buck), PC.5089.2.101; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Calling a Buck))
    - Winged (September 1921 Calendar), PC.5089.2.102; Stick, Frank (Item Winged (September 1921 Calendar))
    - The Home Trail (January 1917 Calendar), PC.5089.2.103; Stick, Frank (Item The Home Trail (January 1917 Calendar))
    - Good Hunting (August 1917 Calendar), PC.5089.2.104; Stick, Frank (Item Good Hunting (August 1917 Calendar))
    - An Autumn Ramble (August 1921 Calendar), PC.5089.2.105; Stick, Frank (Item An Autumn Ramble (August 1921 Calendar))
    - His Last Rush (September 1917 Calendar), PC.5089.2.106; Stick, Frank (Item His Last Rush (September 1917 Calendar))
    - Unexpected (November 1917 Calendar), PC.5089.2.107; Stick, Frank (Item Unexpected (November 1917 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Shooting at Ducks), PC.5089.2.108; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Shooting at Ducks))
    - A Stiff Rift (August 1916 Calendar), PC.5089.2.109; Stick, Frank (Item A Stiff Rift (August 1916 Calendar))
    - A Good Head (April 1917 Calendar), PC.5089.2.110; Stick, Frank (Item A Good Head (April 1917 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Two Men at Campsite Watching a Buck), PC.5089.2.111; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men at Campsite Watching a Buck))
    - Fetch (May 1917 Calendar), PC.5089.2.112; Stick, Frank (Item Fetch (May 1917 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Man Hunting with Two Dogs), PC.5089.2.113; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man Hunting with Two Dogs))
    - Untitled (Two Dos and Man with Gun), PC.5089.2.114; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Dos and Man with Gun))
    - The River Men, PC.5089.2.115; Stick, Frank (Item The River Men)
    - Untitled (Man Hunting in Woods with Dog), PC.5089.2.116; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man Hunting in Woods with Dog))
    - Untitled (Two Men Catching a Fish with a Net), PC.5089.2.117; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Catching a Fish with a Net))
    - Breaking the Jam, PC.5089.2.118; Stick, Frank (Item Breaking the Jam)
    - Steady, PC.5089.2.119; Stick, Frank (Item Steady)
    - Field and Stream October 1913 Cover, PC.5089.2.120; Stick, Frank (Item Field and Stream October 1913 Cover)
    - Riflemen of the Miami Cover, PC.5089.2.121; Stick, Frank (Item Riflemen of the Miami Cover)
    - Untitled (Man Fighting Bear), PC.5089.2.122; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man Fighting Bear))
    - Playtime, PC.5089.2.123; Stick, Frank (Item Playtime)
    - The Best Tonic (July 1916 Calendar), PC.5089.2.124; Stick, Frank (Item The Best Tonic (July 1916 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Mountain Lion and Bears Fighting), PC.5089.2.125; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Mountain Lion and Bears Fighting))
    - The Thundering Hero, PC.5089.2.126; Stick, Frank (Item The Thundering Hero)
    - Untitled (Man, Boy, and Dog Hunting in the Snow), PC.5089.2.127; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man, Boy, and Dog Hunting in the Snow))
    - Chance for a Double (September 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.128; Stick, Frank (Item Chance for a Double (September 1923 Calendar))
    - The Silver King (March 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.129; Stick, Frank (Item The Silver King (March 1923 Calendar))
    - False Friends (November 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.130; Stick, Frank (Item False Friends (November 1923 Calendar))
    - The Final Leap (May 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.131; Stick, Frank (Item The Final Leap (May 1923 Calendar))
    - A Kin to the Eagle (December 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.132; Stick, Frank (Item A Kin to the Eagle (December 1923 Calendar))
    - King of the Pool (April 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.133; Stick, Frank (Item King of the Pool (April 1923 Calendar))
    - Calling the Moose (March 1921 Calendar), PC.5089.2.134; Stick, Frank (Item Calling the Moose (March 1921 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Hunting Ducks), PC.5089.2.135; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Hunting Ducks))
    - On Guard, PC.5089.2.136; Stick, Frank (Item On Guard)
    - Untitled (Two Men with a Canoe Watching a Moose), PC.5089.2.137; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men with a Canoe Watching a Moose))
    - Untitled (Group of People Fighting on a Ship), PC.5089.2.138; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Group of People Fighting on a Ship))
    - Untitled (Two Men Hunting Two Ducks), PC.5089.2.139; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Hunting Two Ducks))
    - A Big Grizzly (October 1917 Calendar), PC.5089.2.140; Stick, Frank (Item A Big Grizzly (October 1917 Calendar))
    - Surprised, PC.5089.2.141; Stick, Frank (Item Surprised)
    - A Record Head (August 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.142; Stick, Frank (Item A Record Head (August 1923 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Buck by a Stream), PC.5089.2.143; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Buck by a Stream))
    - Two of a Kind (October 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.144; Stick, Frank (Item Two of a Kind (October 1923 Calendar))
    - Hooked (July 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.145; Stick, Frank (Item Hooked (July 1923 Calendar))
    - A Chance for Dinner (January 1923 Calendar), PC.5089.2.146; Stick, Frank (Item A Chance for Dinner (January 1923 Calendar))
    - Untitled (Two Dogs with Man Hunting in Meadow), PC.5089.2.147; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Dogs with Man Hunting in Meadow))
    - Shooting the Rapids, PC.5089.2.148; Stick, Frank (Item Shooting the Rapids)
    - Untitled (Man and Woman on Horseback with Dog), PC.5089.2.149; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man and Woman on Horseback with Dog))
    - The Homeward Trail, PC.5089.2.150; Stick, Frank (Item The Homeward Trail)
    - Ready for Battle, PC.5089.2.151; Stick, Frank (Item Ready for Battle)
    - Their Christmas Dinner, PC.5089.2.152; Stick, Frank (Item Their Christmas Dinner)
    - God's Country, PC.5089.2.153; Stick, Frank (Item God's Country)
    - Untitled (Fish Leaping, Three Men in a Boat), PC.5089.2.154; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Fish Leaping, Three Men in a Boat))
    - There's Many a Slip, PC.5089.2.155; Stick, Frank (Item There's Many a Slip)
    - His First Pickerel, PC.5089.2.156; Stick, Frank (Item His First Pickerel)
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Duck Blind, One Smoking a Pipe, One Placing a Decoy), PC.5089.2.157; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Duck Blind, One Smoking a Pipe, One Placing a Decoy))
    - Untitled (Man Hunting Ducks with his Dog), PC.5089.2.158; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man Hunting Ducks with his Dog))
    - Untitled (Man in a Pond, Smoking a Pipe, Man, Dog, and Boat in Background), PC.5089.2.159; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man in a Pond, Smoking a Pipe, Man, Dog, and Boat in Background))
    - Untitled (Man Falling in Water, Second Man Laughing), PC.5089.2.160; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man Falling in Water, Second Man Laughing))
    - Western Metallic Ammunition Advertisement, PC.5089.2.161; Stick, Frank (Item Western Metallic Ammunition Advertisement)
    - Untitled (Two Men Fishing in Boat, Fish Leaping from Water), PC.5089.2.162; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Fishing in Boat, Fish Leaping from Water))
    - Open Season, PC.5089.2.163; Stick, Frank (Item Open Season)
    - Untitled (Man Catching a Fish with a Net, Second Man in Background), PC.5089.2.164; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man Catching a Fish with a Net, Second Man in Background))
    - Untitled (Two Men Camping, Cooking Breakfast, Flipping a Pancake), PC.5089.2.165; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Camping, Cooking Breakfast, Flipping a Pancake))
    - Untitled (Sailors Escape a Burning Ship in a Lifeboat), PC.5089.2.166; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Sailors Escape a Burning Ship in a Lifeboat))
    - Untitled (Two Men Hunting Rabbits in the Snow), PC.5089.2.167; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men Hunting Rabbits in the Snow))
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Wave to Two Men by a Campfire), PC.5089.2.168; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe Wave to Two Men by a Campfire))
    - Untitled (Man Hunting with Dog), PC.5089.2.169; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Man Hunting with Dog))
    - Untitled (Two Men on Horseback Shoot at a Bear), PC.5089.2.170; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men on Horseback Shoot at a Bear))
    - Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe, Fish Leaping in Background), PC.5089.2.171; Stick, Frank (Item Untitled (Two Men in a Canoe, Fish Leaping in Background))
    - Unexpected, PC.5089.2.172; Stick, Frank (Item Unexpected)
    - Hard Luck!, PC.5089.2.173; Stick, Frank (Item Hard Luck!)
    - Autumn Days, PC.5089.2.174; Stick, Frank (Item Autumn Days)
    - Long Key, PC.5089.2.175; Stick, Frank (Item Long Key)
    - Surf Off New Jersey Coast, PC.5089.2.176; Stick, Frank (Item Surf Off New Jersey Coast)
    - Mississippi Valley, PC.5089.2.177; Stick, Frank (Item Mississippi Valley)
    - Herrings Fishermen, PC.5089.2.178; Stick, Frank (Item Herrings Fishermen)
    - Out of the Fog, PC.5089.2.179; Stick, Frank (Item Out of the Fog)
    - A Following Wind, PC.5089.2.180; Stick, Frank (Item A Following Wind)
    - Sunset In Iowa, PC.5089.2.181; Stick, Frank (Item Sunset In Iowa)
    - Maine Woods, PC.5089.2.182; Stick, Frank (Item Maine Woods)